SHIVAM CHAUDHARY

Operations Manager

Email:

nzshivamchaudhary@gmail.com **Tel:** +91 9773889996 An experienced <u>Business & Management Professional</u> with <u>6+ Years of Experience in Management & Operations</u>. A professional attitude and an ability to be flexible and handle change in a positive manner. <u>Have done Bachelors of Applied Management</u> (<u>operations& production management</u>). Looking for suitable job in <u>Business Development</u>, <u>Operations Management</u>, and <u>Customer Service</u>, <u>Contact Centre</u> or related position with a growing organization where my technical aptitude and problem solving ability will enhance technical support and benefit operational efficiencies. To enhance my strengths and skills and to provide excellent solution to customers with my Skills, Work experience and Oualification.

WORK EXPERIENCE

51 Pages Road Accommodations-Facilities Manager

Christchurch, NZ – September 2018- February 2020

Organizing and coordinating the strategic and operational management of buildings and facilities in public and private organizations to ensure the proper and efficient operation of all physical aspects of a facility, to create and sustain safe and productive environments for occupants.

Woolston Sports Bar- Operations Manager

Christchurch, NZ – February 2019- February 2020

Planning and organising special functions. Arranging the purchasing and pricing of goods according to budget maintaining records of stock levels and financial transactions. Ensuring dining facilities comply with health regulations and are clean, functional and of suitable appearance.

Mackenzies Hotel/ Bar- Operations Manager

Christchurch, NZ-September 2018- June 2019

Observing liquor, gaming, and other laws and regulations. Assessing and reviewing customer satisfaction. Ensuring compliance with occupational health and safety regulations. Providing guests with local tourism information, and arrange tours and transportation.

Little Saigon Vietnamese Restaurant–Restaurant Manager

Christchurch, NZ- December 2015- August 2018

Planning and organising special functions. Arranging the purchasing and pricing of goods according to budget. Maintaining records of stock levels and financial transactions. Ensuring dining facilities comply with health regulations and are clean, functional and of suitable appearance.

Little Saigon Vietnamese Restaurant- Assistant Manager

Christchurch, NZ- April 2013- December 2015

Planning and coordinating day to day restaurant operations in conjunction with Manger and head chef.

EDUCATION

- ≥ 2009-2011 : Air Force Golden Jubilee Institute- High School
- > 2012-2015 : Ara Institute of Canterbury, Bachelor of Applied Management (operations & production), Christchurch, New Zealand

KEY SKILLS

- Understand all legal, regulatory, information security and compliance requirements.
- Achieving targets in a dynamic and complex business environment.
- Ability to manage and develop a diverse group of highly skilled people.
- A pragmatic approach to getting the required results.
- ► Ability to manage operations within budgetary constraints.
- Building and maintaining strong and effective relationships with suppliers and Customer
- ► Proficient in Internet Skills, MS Office Suite
- ► Building a rapport and relationship with customers.

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi